where do you live ukraine the city of khmelnitsky you are
где живете украина город хмельницкое вы
from russia where and russia in russia is
из россии откуда а россия в россии это
one speed city king you don’t know
одну скорость город король не знаете
this well let’s try
такой а ну давайте попробуем
try let’s be jewish were bizhan
попробуйте давайте еврейского были бижан
wanted to
хотел
know in general the name of this city I
знать вообще название этого города я на
don’t even know where it is located there near the
есть даже знаю где находится там возле
seaside region seams,
приморского края швы ,
just
просто
obscene happens to
матерные бывает
you in the Jewish Autonomous Region there are
вас еврейской автономной области там
only a couple of percent of Jews living there, and
евреев пару процентов только живет а
[music]
[музыка]
I’m how old I am 41 years old I was born 81 years old
мне сколько мне 41 год я 81 года
back in the Soviet Union,
рождения еще при советском союзе жилы
how did you remember the map of the Soviet Union there I
как вы карту советского союза помню там
looked at the atlas and the republics were
смотрела атлас был и республики были
bad or
плохие или а
why are you over there  such proin discount
почему вас вон там такой proin скидки
pika exactly cool even click
пику точно прикольная даже жмите а
why are you there background such a kitchen
почему вас там фон такая кухня
kitchen I just have a bottle that this is my
у меня просто флакону что это мой
sweet country I am proud of it
сладкий страны я им горжусь
you are proud of the kitchen after the kitchen on
вы гордитесь кухне после кухню на
[laughter]
[смех]
shows
показывает а
but look at the sound from russia ask
вот смотрите звук из россии спрашивай
how you feel about the war  keep in ukraine,
как вы относитесь к войне в украине
yes, explain why you are sitting right
держите да вот объясните почему вы сидя
there,
вот там
okay, here you are with you from there from Birobidzhan
окей вот вы с вами оттуда из биробиджана
and the Jewish auton  omnoy region so an hour
и еврейской автономной области так час
you are here in russia so why do you
вас носит тут по россии так почему вам
need this war here personally
нужна эта война вот лично вам
I personally don’t need it but I
мне лично она не нужна но я ее
support it well that’s why you
поддерживать ну вот почему вы поддержите
support you have this motivation because it’s
у вас есть это мотивация потому что это
my country the
моя страна
government made this choice I
правительство сделало этот выбор я
voted the
голосовала
cult understood  yes you look you are just
культа понял да вы смотрите вы как раз
interesting in the Jewish autonomous region
интересно в еврейской автономной области
you live you remember during the second
живете вы помните во время второй
world war it was like this I don’t remember me
мировой войны был такой я не помню меня
there wasn’t
не было
you remember how you taught at school that in the
вы помните вы как учили в школе что в
thirty-ninth year Russia is building a
тридцать девятом году россия строим
world war so hitler such y
мировая война так гитлером такой у
should be Austrian yes  and he killed Jews
должна австрийский да и он убивал евреев
burned there
сжигал там
it turned out yes it turns out there was
получилось да так получается там сидела
also some girl in germany sitting there with
тоже какая-то девушка в германии там с
pigtails such things I support the
косичками такие дела я поддерживаю
killing of Jews because this is my
убийство евреев потому что это моя
country I chose and
страна я избрала и
killed it turns out they didn’t leave you killed them
убили получается они не ушли вы их убили
we threw a rocket what they are  they
мы кинули ракету то что они там
were there they were warned once they were
оказались их предупредили раз
warned 2 they didn’t understand yes understood
предупредили 2 не поняли да понятую
seppo you are so cold-bloodedly ready to kill
сеппо вы так хладнокровно готовы убивать
civilians I’m not ready to kill
мирных жителей я никого не готовы
anyone  Are you ready to support the
убивать вы готовы поддерживать
killings
убийствами
I’m not ready to support the killing of civilians
я не готова поддержки убийства мирных
wait you
подождите вы
don’t kill civilians they hit if they
не убиваем мирных они попали если они
hit
попали
it turns out that there is and you think
именно получается что есть а вы думаете
in Russia they don’t kill anyone
в россии никого не убивают
in Russia we didn’t attack you you
в россии мы на вас не нападали вы напали
attacked our country on
на нашу страну на
let’s give it interesting  since the
давайте давайте подарим интересно раз
company what we did
компании что мы делали
now tell me from what date of my
теперь скажите с какого числа моих
beginning of
начале
2014 and here and
2014 года а вот и так
since it was probably
как это был наверное
here I will
вот я вам скажу 2 12 апреля 2014 года
tell you  into the territory of
стрелковым оружием вошли на территорию
Ukraine, that is, the Donetsk region, and
украины то есть донецкой области и
captured the city of Slavyansk, further
захватили город славянск дальше еще
brigades went in, they still captured Slavyansk, they still
бригады заходили захватывали до сих пор
haven’t taken someone
славянск не взяли кого-то
girl again, I understand that you
девушка еще раз вы я понимаю что у вас
really like this phrase so
такое словосочетание очень нравится так
let’s try to speak
давайте попробуем по-русски поговорить
in Russian so not in French  and once again, yes, here on
так не по-французски и еще раз да вот 12
April 12, 2013, the
апреля 2013 года
story is
история
so say until April 12, 14, while the
так скажите до 12 апреля 14 года пока
Russian militant  and they didn’t come to the Donbass
российские боевики не пришли на донбасс
from the territory of Russia or
из территории россии или кто-то там
someone killed someone there, you can name at least
кого-то убивал можете мне назвать хоть
one person killed before 2006, it’s not
одного убитого до 2006 года не что это
yours to shell when I say tell
ваш обстреливать когда я скажу скажите
me how
мне ладу
on April 12 your militants and Russians
12 апреля ваши боевики и российские
entered the territory of Ukraine.
вошли на территорию украины .
read it, take it, take the shooters
почитайте возьмите вот возьмите стрелков
in the Russian alphabet, I
в русском алфавите
thought about the dream, well-
задумалась на видно сон начитанная
read erudition, and I’m her is one letter or
начитанность а я ее это одна буква или
different e.yu.  i its
разные е.ю. я ее
certainly different
конечно разные
wrong there ea
неправильно там е.а.
and
и
on the design and where are you afraid of people for
на дизайна и на где ты боишься люди на
oil and the wife with intelligence and
нефть а жена интеллектом и
such we really have sums for a tractor tone
таким у нас правде сумм на трактор тон
here
вот
on a cynical skateboard on a cynical skateboard it
на скейте цинично на скейте циничного на
can come out when we are on top and there part of the
может выйти когда мы верху и там часть
time yes we attack then he and sumi cho
времени да мы нападаем то он и суми чо
attacked  ukraine
напавшие на украину
sometimes you
бывает ты
alla pour whiskey from chicken also our
алла налить висков из курицы тоже нашей
he clinics
он клиник
no one may right conclusion and we are ukrainian
никто не мая право вывод и нас украинец
and
и
autocratic empire will bends jim
самовластно империя будет излучины джим
breaks off on the axis of such [ __ ] what are
отрывается на ось таких калечат каковы
each tire on time so
каждой шины на времени так
she is petr i'm a cool and hitler go there
она петр i'm a cool и гитлер там бываю
for everyone  like if this one and the leader before the
на каждого типа если этот и лидер до
loop breaks off, here I am for him at the trunk of
отрыва петлю вот я за него у ствола из
such cynical you, the jerk is rounded by the
таких циничных ты рывок скругляется
fangs of the drill of the empire and kim means
клыки бур империи и ким ему саму значит
to him in Ukraine
по украине
and poke around
и по суйтесь
such a montage, like and sign
такой монтаж ставьте лайк и подписон
my channel as a killer, we will lubricate
киллером канал моей будем смажет